

With an entrepreneur mindset, a dreamer and technology lover, will be helping you achieve your goals and grow. Full Stack developer with 7+ years experience in JavaScript, Angular, React, node.js, .NET and other web technologies. Excellent at developing custom web applications, setting up servers and maintaining them over time. Eager to learn new technologies and apply them in world-class projects. An excellent fit for your established work process and procedures. or will readily advise and help you build proper ones.

SUMMARY

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality- Indian Address-Munich, Germany

CONTACT



inolassingh@gmail.com



+49 1624537445



salonisinghfullstackengg



<u>Inolas05</u>

LANGUAGE

- English
- German

SALONI SINGH

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (https://portfolio-inolas.netlify.app/)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

KNOWIS AG

April 2022- Present

Development and maintenance of credit management solutions offered to multiple financial institutions. My role is to design and maintain the frontend template which reduces the cost, time and provides transparency to all the stakeholders.

• Design Engineer

SEAGATE TECHNOLOGY

January 2016-February 2018

Associated with the SSD development department. My responsibilities included: Design, development and maintenance of the web applications. Front end development with JavaScript, HTML5, CSS. Building an internal web portal for tracking and tracing different components of SSD. Modifying source code to enhance stability and to fix defects.

• Full Stack Developer

FREELANCE

March 2018-March 2022

1) Fin-tech Project - Company based out of USA developing banking authentication software. My role was to implement authentication and authorization mechanisms for the software. Tools used - JavaScript, Node.js, Postman, Express.js, Git. 2)E-commerce Project - Company based out of USA having multiple brand apparel products whose customer base is USA. My role was to design the inventory and in memory search functionality for the product .Tools used - JavaScript, Node.js, React, CSS flexbox, Git

Freelance

PERSONAL PROJECTS

March 2018-March 2022

1) Smart-Brain: A face recognition app using an Artificial Intelligence API.(https://github.com/inolas05/Smartbrain)(https://github.com/inolas05/smartbrain_api)
2) Robo-Friends: (https://github.com/inolas05/Robofriends-App)
A real time search app that fetches data from 2 different APIs.

EDUCATION

B.Tech (Electronics & Communication Engineering)
 MANIPAL ACADEMY OF HIGHER EDUCATION

July 2012-July 2016

SKILLS

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- ES6
- Angular
- React + Redux
- Responsive Design
- HTML/HTML5
- CSS3 + Flexbox
- .NET/Node.js
- Entity Framework

- Express.js
- C++/C#
- RESTful API
- Nginx
- SQL
- Mongo DB
- Postman
- GIT/Gitlab
- Agile (Scrum)

- Jenkins
- Jira
- Unit Testing
- Cypress